<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mooqita</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mooqita</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Mooqita.com, content license unless otherwise noted &lt;a href=&#39;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Mooqita/mooqita.github.io/master/LICENSE&#39; target=&#39;_blank&#39;&gt;CC-NC-BY-SA&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 01:07:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mooqita Welcomes New Team Members</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/07/05/2018-07-18_newteammembers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 01:07:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/07/05/2018-07-18_newteammembers/</guid>
      <description>Meet Anna and Celina - our new interns Mooqita would like to introduce and welcome two new interns to be a part of the Mooqita team this summer. In the past month, Mooqita joined forces with Valleyworx in the Central Valley to find great interns. ValleyWorx is a tech and digital design coworking space in Modesto California that attracts and deems to grow local talent as well as the local tech community in the valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Round at SkyDeck</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/06/25/2018-06-25_mooqitaatskydeck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 01:07:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/06/25/2018-06-25_mooqitaatskydeck/</guid>
      <description>Mooqita at Skydeck The Mooqita team is excited to take part in another round as a Hot Desk team at SkyDeck. SkyDeck is a UC Berkeley startup accelerator and incubator that was formed through the collaboration of the Haas School of Business, College of Engineering and the Office of the Vice Chancellor for Research. Its office is located on the penthouse floor of the highest building in downtown Berkeley, and it encompasses a facility for collaboration within an open workspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mooqita at CHI &#39;18</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/06/19/2018-06-19_mooqitaatchi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 01:07:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/06/19/2018-06-19_mooqitaatchi/</guid>
      <description>Mooqita is happy to announce that our team’s case study submission was accepted and published at CHI 2018, the ACM Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems. CHI is the premier international conference on human-computer interaction that brings forth researchers and practitioners to discuss advances in interactive technology. This year the conference took place from April 21st – April 26st in Montréal Canada, and our Mooqita team members Markus Krause and Jan Smeddinck attended and represented the team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mooqita for Educators in Detail</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/09/26/2017-09-26_valuepropositioneducators/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 01:07:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/09/26/2017-09-26_valuepropositioneducators/</guid>
      <description>Mooqita is a platform that connects organizations, learners, and educators, creating meaningful learning experiences by solving real world work tasks. We help your learners to transfer the knowledge and skills you teach them into real world experience by enabling them to solve tasks that come from companies we work with. In the process, the students improve their soft skills by working on larger projects that can&amp;rsquo;t be solved alone, fostering team work, and communication in multicultural groups across different time zones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Successes</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/09/06/2017-09-06_firstsuccesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/09/06/2017-09-06_firstsuccesses/</guid>
      <description>We are conducting our first test run with the beta system and have some preliminary results. A total of 158 Students from the BerkeleyX Ruby online course on EdX accessed our website for the experiment. From 88 (~55%) of these students started the challenge, 14 (9%) submitted a solution, and 12 (8%) solutions were correct (solved the challenge), 6 (5%) Students submitted a solution for the second challenge and were invited for the paid group assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mooqita for Organizations in Detail</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/09/01/2017-09-01_valuepropositionorganizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 01:07:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/09/01/2017-09-01_valuepropositionorganizations/</guid>
      <description>Mooqita is a platform that connects organizations, learners, and educators, creating meaningful learning experiences by solving real world work tasks. We match your organization with capable and highly motivated learners by letting them solve tasks that are crucial in your day-to-day operations. This builds up a pool of tested potential hires for you. As another result of this process you help create relevant work experience for our learners in a field of their interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Upgrade Hiring to the 21st Century: AI &amp;amp; data science for diversity awareness, skill and personality matching Mooqita is a platform that offers a new approach to hiring. Tired of scanning through resumes? Hire the smartest talents from all backgrounds, who can solve problems and match your team. Our method lifts pre-screening to a new level and selects the talents that matter to your business.
How it works Through our onboarding process we learn what companies are looking for in terms of tasks they need done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our platform?
Please feel free to contact us, while we are starting our operations we do not yet have a customer service center working 24&amp;frasl;7, but we will do our best to get back to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Mooqita is firmly rooted in research. Our collaborators keep on pushing the envelope of research on online learning and crowdsourcing technologies every day. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/</guid>
      <description>Mooqita is made possible by our wonderful core team and supported by cooperators around the globe. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>